Guide to the Southern African Research Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Southern African Research Program, Yale University, records
1977-1994
RU 157
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
10
(8 boxes)
The records consist of seminar papers, workshop papers, and administrative files documenting the Southern African Research Program at Yale.
Yale University. Southern African Research Program
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-C (YRG 3-C), Records of Yale academic divisions, councils, and committees.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of seminar papers, workshop papers, and administrative files documenting the Southern African Research Program at Yale.
Africa, Southern -- Study and teaching; Yale University. Southern African Research Program
- Seminar and workshop papers and administrative records, 1977-1994; Accession 1994-A-135
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 1-6 contain original works that require written permission of the author or copyright holder to copy. Boxes 7 and 8 are closed until 2030 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
  - Seminar papers
    - 1977-1981 (Box 1)
    - 1981-1984 (Box 2)
    - 1984-1987 (Box 3)
    - 1987-1990 (Box 4)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 6)
    - 1990-1993 (Box 5)
    - 1994 (Box 7)
  - Workshop papers, 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Administrative records, 1977-1993 (Box 7–8)
    Restricted until Jan 1, 2030.